(Sheldon:)That's ridiculous.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Why? You never thought
(Raj:)you'd end up in a relationship,
(Raj:)and then you met Amy.
(Raj:)Maybe there's someone else
out there for you.
(Sheldon:)True, but Penny's married,
and so is Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)And your girlfriend has
red hair and white skin,
(Sheldon:)which really rubs up
against my clown phobia.
(Leonard:)Maybe you should consider women
(Leonard:)who aren't
in serious relationships
(Leonard:)with your closest friends?
(Sheldon:)There's that prostate doctor,
but I'm still mad at her.
(Sheldon:)Oh, there's a woman.
Oh, I'll make her my girlfriend.
(Raj:)Whoa, whoa.
(Raj:)Walking up to a strange woman
in a bar usually doesn't work.
(Sheldon:)You're forgetting something.
(Sheldon:)Ladies love jocks.
(Raj:)How many sips
of that beer did he have?
(Sheldon:)Three.
Oh, boy.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me. I'm recovering
from a recent breakup,
(Sheldon:)and I'm told asking out another
woman might make me feel better.
(Sheldon:)And as Ash Ketchum said
to Pikachu, "I choose you."